So you built a number of web sites.
你构建了大量网站
You know HTML, which provides this structure for a site.
了解为网站提供结构的 HTML
You've used CSS to style sites and make them look good.
使用 CSS 为网站设置样式 使其看起来美观
You've got it some nice font,
你添加了一些看起来不错的字体
a splash of color here.
偶尔设置一些颜色
You've also learned the greatest programming language in the world.
你还学习了世界上最精彩的编程语言
It's obviously JavaScript, but how did the worlds of
当然是 JavaScript
HTML and CSS and the world of JavaScript come together?
但是 HTML CSS 和 JavaScript 如何组合到一起呢?
Well, that is exactly what you will be learning about in this course.
这正是你在这门课程中将学习的知识
HTML and CSS are fantastic at what they do.
HTML 和 CSS 都很强大
The problem is that they are kind of static.
问题是 它们属于静态语言
Once you write the HTML for a page,
当你为网页编写 HTML 后
it does not change.
它就不会改变了
That scintillating purple background color you added to the footer element,
你向页脚元素中添加的闪耀紫色背景
unless you change it in the style sheet,
始终都会是紫色
it is always going to be that shade of purple.
除非在样式表中进行修改
Static, it is kind of boring.
静态有点枯燥
We want change, we want motion,
我们希望有改变 希望有动态效果
and we want to control them programmatically.
并且希望能通过编程方式进行控制
In this course, you will learn to use JavaScript and a new web
在这门课程中 你将学习如何使用 JavaScript
API called the DOM to control the website.
和一个叫做 DOM 的网络 API 控制网站
Being able to control the way a website responds to
能够控制网站对用户做出响应的方式
its users is a fundamental skill of a web developer,
是 Web 开发者应具备的基本技能
and you do not have to go very far on the web to see it in action either.
这些功能在网上很常见
An image slider, most kinds of form validation, a rating system,
图片滑块 大多数表单验证 评分系统
commenting system, all of these are powered by the skills you will learn,
评论系统都采用了你将学习的技能
but let me highlight just a few of them.
我来概括下其中的几个技能
You will learn about the DOM,
你将学习 DOM
how to update and style page content.
了解如何更新网页内容并设置样式
You will learn about the hidden world of
你将了解浏览器事件
browser events and how to hook into them and respond to them.
以及如何监听事件并作出响应
You will also learn about the JavaScript event loop,
你还将学习 JavaScript 事件循环
which will help you to write better, more performing code.
这会帮助你编写性能更强的代码
Now, why should I be teaching you about all of this?
为何由我来讲解所有这些知识呢?
I am Richard Kalehoff, a Senior Content Developer here at
我是 Richard Kalehoff 优达学城高级内容开发工程师
Udacity and the Curriculum Lead for the front-end Nanodegree program.
以及前端纳米学位的课程主管
I have been developing on the web for,
我已经有 哇 超过 10 年的 Web 开发经验
I have also taught this content for years at the graduate level,
并且多年来都以毕业生水平讲解这些内容
and I actually use this stuff every single day.
实际上我每天都会用到这些技能
For example, there is a site I use all the time to watch some educational videos,
例如 我经常在一个网站上观看一些教育类视频
but the instructor talks way too slowly for me,
但是对我来说 这些视频的讲课速度太慢了
but there is no option or button to change the speed of the video.
没有什么选项或按钮可以更改视频速度
That is not a problem though. Using the skills in this course,
但这并不是问题 运用这门课程中的技能
I create my own button and I am able to alter the speed of the video.
我自己创建了一个按钮 能够更改视频速度
I can jump forward or backward in time.
我可以快进或快退
So, see, this skills are incredibly useful. Let's get started.最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6
所以说 这些技能非常实用 我们开始吧。最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6